A Guide to the Linda Wilkinson Bock Papers, 1848-1999
Library of Virginia
- Pamphlets, Magazines, etc. (Box 17)
  - Souvenir of the Exercises of the Hanover Monument to Confederate Soldiers, 27 August 1914 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - The Red Cross Courier, 15 August 1929 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - John Tyler, an Address of the Hon. Claude G. Bowers of New York, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - A Committee Report Made to the Bar Association of the City of Richmond, Virginia, Commemorating the Life of the Late Edmund Waddill, Jr., One of the Judges of the Fourth Circuit Court of Appeals of the United States, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Report on the Economic Conditions of the South, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Anaconda Wire, April 1951 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Advance Sheets of Cases Decided in the Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - The Spire, Charles City, Virginia, March 1952 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 300th Anniversary of the Founding of Surry County, 1652-1952 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kiplinger Magazine, November 1956 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - The Jamestown Festival Official Program, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlets (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Plays and miscellaneous items (Box 17, Folder 23)